getit.co.in 2013-11-24

# Local Brand Search India, Local Business Brand Search, Online Brand Search, Online Business Brand Search, Local Search Engine, India

  | 

Privacy Policy

This privacy policy applies to your use of the GETIT website, www.getit.in (hereafter known as GETIT), GETIT's mobile website, m.getit.in and GETIT applications on mobile platforms (Android, iPhone, BlackBerry, Windows Phone, Nokia), but not does apply to any third party sites that may be linked to them, or any relationships you may have with the businesses listed on GETIT. By using GETIT, you agree to the terms of this privacy policy. 

Asking for your information

We will sometimes ask clients for personal information such as you name, address, e-mail address, occupation, hobbies and other details. Providing us your information will simply help us offer products and services that we think you'd like to hear about. When you choose to give personal information to us over the Internet that we or our business partners may request, we will endeavor to inform you how we will use the information. When we ask for personal information for any reason, we will provide a link to this policy statement to make our intentions clear. We record information relating to your use of GETIT, such as the searches you undertake, the pages you view, and timestamp. For mobile platforms, we use Geo Coordinates from your device to get current location info like CityName. Application then sets default CityName OR you can set a different city from the list. We use this info to get your location and serve more relevant data. We use this type of information to administer GETIT and provide the highest possible level of service to you. We do not use location info for any other purpose other than localizing search results. You cannot be identified from this aggregate information. 

Personal Information Privacy

GETIT Infoservices(P) Ltd will take all appropriate steps to keep your personal information confidential. Those steps include limiting access to client information databases, communicating this policy statement to all GETIT Infoservices(P) Ltd employees and establishing and enforcing penalties for violating this statement. GETIT Infoservices(P) Ltd will not sell, rent, or give away our clients' personal information to other companies for them to use in selling others' products or services. When we do contract with another company to market or advertise products or services for us, we will insist on binding agreements from those companies protecting our client information. We will vigorously enforce all privacy agreements we have with other companies. We gather personal information from our clients so we can better develop our relationship with those clients. Occasionally, we seek client comments on our products and services. These comments allow us to determine which products and services our clients should be made aware of based on their specific needs. We will communicate with clients via e-mail or other online delivery devices only if the client agrees to receive those communications. Clients, who believe they are receiving our communications in error or no longer desire to receive them, should inform us and we will remove those clients' names from our mailing lists. GETIT Infoservices(P) Ltd will be judicious in the use of e-mail and paper mail to communicate with clients. We will, at all times, put ourselves in the place of the recipients of our mail and treat our clients as we ourselves would like to be treated. GETIT Infoservices(P) Ltd has teamed with others to provide our clients with enhanced Internet services. In providing such services, our business partners also may request personal information from our clients. We prohibit these business partners from selling or giving away our client information and we require them to have a posted Privacy Policy, so that our clients may review it before providing personal information to our business partners.

Cookies

GETIT Infoservices(P) Ltd currently uses a "cookie" on our site. No cookies are placed on the user's computer. A cookie is placed on our server for as long as the session is active. No data from the user's computer is accessed from our site. Our cookies tag each visitor's browser with a random, unique number. The cookie simply assigns a number and does not disclose any personal information about the person using the browser. By noting where these uniquely numbered browsers go on our site, we can study traffic patterns and improve our site.

Contact us

For any further information or assistance in joining our platform, kindly write to us at [info@getitinfomedia.in](mailto:info@getitinfomedia.in)

|
